there were peace negotiations after this war
мирные переговоры были после этой войны
What kind of peace negotiations Crimean What were the
Какие мирные переговоры Крымский Какие
Crimean war field And when was the
кры поле Крымской войны А когда была
Crimean war after the Crimean in
Крымская война после Крымского в 20144
20144 [ __ ] starts again
году бля опять начинается
hello I'm St. Petersburg Where are you
здравствуйте я санкт-петербурга Вы
from I'm from Rostov myself But I've
откуда Я сам родом из Ростова Но 18 лет
been living in California for 18 years in 2 years  in the
живу в Калифорнии через 2 года будет
twentieth, St. Petersburg came to study or
двадцатом Петербург приехали учиться или
were born there to study And where did they come
родились там учиться А откуда приехали
from Tula, but you don’t Slavic appearance
из Тулы по у вас не Славянская внешность
seemed to me there Dagestan Possibly or
мне показалось там Дагестан Возможно или
Well, my
Ну у меня
father is Dagestan And my mother is Russian
отец дагестанец А мать русская
Dagestan who exactly is an Avar Kumyk
дагестанец кто именно аварец кумык
Dargin Lak Tabasaran Avar
даргинец лакец табасаранец аварец аварец
Avar Avar A Basra Netz is not a Tabasaran
аварец А басра нец есть табасаранец не
Russian nationality Tabasaran Yes
обосра нец национальность табасаранец Да
Tabasaran I understood well Well, you’re definitely
табасаранец я понял хорошо Ну ты точно
from Russia because you
из России потому что ты
don’t know the nationalities that live in Russia
национальности которые живут в России не
media
знаешь СМИ
Well, I just live in Central Russia,
Ну я просто живу в Центральной России
there aren’t really any other nationalities
тут особо нет других национальностей
except some Uzbeks or Well, usually
кроме узбеков каких-нибудь или Ну обычно
in Central Russia there are Uzbeks and  Yes, there
в Центральной России узбеки и чеченцы да
should be Chechens, but basically they’re the only
должны быть но в основном тут только они
ones here in this. The Uzbek diaspora is very
у вас в этом в Узбекская диаспора очень
strong
сильная
in St. Petersburg, and
в Питере ещё ж
this candidate Savu Fedoseev, or how
кандидата этого саву Федосеева или как
he was removed. The Uzbek diaspora removed him from
его сняли Узбекская диаспора сняла его с
the elections. It’s
выборов
cool for you. Well, when I’m 20, what
Прикольно вам с Ну когда мне 20 что
when when there’s only one country?  it’s
когда когда страна одна какая-то се
taking away the best territories, it’s not a sin
забирает лучшие территории это не грех
that a lot of countries will come to it.
того что к ней будут приезжать очень
Well, people from other countries
много стран Ну людей из других стран так
work for a hairdresser in the USA. That’s
в США работает на
cool. What is the name of the
парикмахера Прикольно А как называется
specialty of a hairdresser, a stylist understands and the
специальность парикмахер стилист понял а
World Cup is communicating here. You and the Ukrainians
ЧМ тут общаетесь Вы с украинцами мто
say yes, yes, I do to them  I’m trying to prove
Говорите Да да я им пытаюсь доказать то
that not everyone is here and not everyone wants to
что не все тут ко и не все хотят их
bomb them. Cool. Do you want to bomb them?
бомбить Прикольно А вы хотите их бомбить
No, what do you think?
Нет а как вы считаете Я им показываю Я
How so And how do you
стреляю по украинцам ф Как так А как вы
think whose
считаете чей
Crimea is? Well, Russia She pays for it, my
Крым Ну Россия Она же за него платит моё
state, my state, the USA believes
государство моё государство США считает
that Crimea is Ukraine, all states except
что Крым Украина все государства кроме
Russia believe that Crimea is Ukraine How
Росси счита что Крым - это Украина Как
is it that
так получается что
Russia Uh-huh,
Россия Угу до
tell me how it turns out that
говорите говори как получается что
only Russia considers Crimea  to
только Россия считает Крым
my own Well, now I’ll explain, I’ll try
своим Ну ну сейчас я объясню я попробую
more, I’d like to explain in a smarter language,
более хотелось бы мне более умным языком
but I’ll explain They’re just
объяснить но я объясню Просто
financing Crimea, financing Crimea, Russia is
финансируют Крым финансирует Крым Россия
correct, what does it mean financing Crimea
правильно что значит финансирует Крым
roads, what do they call it, so it’s
дороги б это это называ так это ж по
between the Geneva Conventions Yes, they
между по женевским конвенциям Да
occupy, she’s implementing the Geneva
оккупируют она исполняет женевскую
Convention, she’s  occupied it must
конвенцию она оккупировала она должна
take care of the population in the occupied
заботиться о населении на оккупированной
territory Yes, the Geneva Convention is
территории Да Женевская конвенция об
written about this, just as Ukraine has now
этом написано так же как Украина сейчас
seized part of the Kursk region, it is
захватила часть Курской области она там
the administration of the city of Sudzha Yes And the city of
администрация город Судже Да И город
Sudzha is like that too, yes, well, the city of Sudzha
Суджа типа тоже да ну город Суджа это
is the Kursk region Yes, well, that’s what I’m
есть Курская область Да го Ну я же
saying  that this is Ukraine now, yes if
говорю то что это Украина теперь да если
there are
там Украина
no payments in Ukraine, the war has not yet been won, I’m not
выплат нет война ещё не выиграна я не
saying that there is no Zaporozhye If you
говорю то что запорожска нет Если бы вы
asked Donetsk Donetsk is Russia, I would
спросили Донецк Донецк - это Россия я бы
answer no, but if they asked about Crimea, the war
ответил бы нет а спросили про Крым война
was over. What kind of war was over in
была закончена Какая закончена война в
Crimea? peace negotiations were held  after this
Крыму мирные переговоры были после этой
war What kind of peace negotiations Crimea What
войны Какие мирные переговоры Крым Какие
kry And when was the Crimean war
кры А когда была Крымская война
in 2014 when he was
в 2014 году когда его зах
captured What war of the annex of Crimea happened The
авали Какая война анекса Крыма произошла
Crimean war when the peace negotiations took place
Крымская война когда прошли мирные
what they signed something when
переговоры чем они подписали чтото когда
they were after that the
это были после этого же были подписаны
peace negotiations were signed or no no not  there were
мирные переговоры или нет нет не было
no
нет
sanctions on Russia, they imposed sanctions for the fact
санкции на Россию наложили санкции за то
that it occupied and it is still
что она оккупировала и она до сих пор
trying to squeeze
типа пробует отжать себе
Crimea out of Crimea.
Крым в Крыме
Why is there no Sberbank of Russia in Crimea
Почему в Крыму нету Сбербанка России
if Crimea is Russia, why is there no
если Крым - это Россия почему нету
Sberbank and why is there no
Сбербанка и почему нету
Russian Railways? I think for reasons of sanctions. That is, it
РЖД Я думаю по причинам санкций То есть
turns out  Russia does not recognize Crimea as its
получается Россия не признаёт Крым своей
territory, that the state bank, Yes,
территорией что государственный банк Да
no, probably considers this territory
нет считает наверное э эту территорию
dangerous for the development of business. Well, that is,
опасной для развития бизнеса Ну то есть
for it. So there are
для неё Значит есть
territories that can be considered theirs
территории которые можно считать своими
and which are
а которые
Neya. I think this was done a little
Нея Я думаю это было сделано немножко
for something else, for this whole thing in the
для другого для вот этого всего в
future.  they planned again,
будущем чего они планировали ещё раз
look, the state bank is not a
смотри государственный банк это не
private bank, which I assess the risks Yes, the
частный банк который риски оцениваю Да
state bank must be
государственный банк должен
present on
присутствовать на
the territory of all constituent entities of the Russian
территории всех субъектов Российской
Federation Yes, in Crimea it basically
Федерации Да в Крыму его принципиально
does not exist. What am I asking why is there no state bank of Russia in
государственного банка России нету в
Crimea? How do I know that I am sitting in the
Крыму Я откуда знаю я что сижу в
state or  in the government Good
государстве или в правительстве Хорошо
What is the difference between the fact that now
Чем Чем отличается ээ то что сейчас
Russia controls the territory of Crimea from
Россия контролирует территорию Крыма от
the fact that Ukraine controls the territory of the
того что Украина контролирует территорию
Kursk region, it turns out that the Kurdish
Курской области получается курдская
region is Ukraine now yes Well, let it
область - это Украина теперь да Ну пусть
be so cool Even if we proceed
будет так прикольно Даже Если исходить
from this logic Let it be so Well, according to
из этой логики Пусть будет так Ну я по
your logic It turns out  whoever joined the
вашей логике Получается кто встал в
army already considers it his
войсками тот уже тот уже считает своей
territory, yes
территорией да
Well, I say Let it be so, this is not my
Ну я говорю Пусть будет так это не моя
logic. I’m just saying that, like,
логика Я просто о том что типа
funding has been going there to Russia for the
финансирование туда идёт России на
past 10 years And that for
протяжении уже 10 лет И что на
10 years I’m not mistaken, look
протяжении 10 я же не ошибаюсь смотри
if the person is no one  hasn’t come to this territory
если человек никто на эту территорию не
for 10 years, if
приходит уже на протяжении 10 лет если
yes, if some idiot got into your
да если какой-то [__] залез в твою
apartment, yes, he lives in it, they already
квартиру да вот Живёт в ней тым уже
explained this, yes, you can’t kick him out for 10 years,
объясняли это да ты его 10 лет не можешь
yes, he’s doing renovations there, and so
выгнать Да он там ремонт делает и так
on, it’s his apartment or  No, you
дальше это его квартира или нет Ты же
can kick him out of there
его можешь оттуда выгнать
correctly, you can. If you have the power
правильно можешь Если у тебя есть сила
to kick him out, you have thousands of ways to
выгнать у тебя у тебя тысячи способов
kick him out. You are this state, this is the very
его выгнать ты это государство это само
state
государство
of the year. Right now, right now, the
года Вот именно сейчас да сейчас и
process has begun. Ukraine first, that’s
начался процесс Украина сначала вот
when they first come and say Yes, the
когда сначала приходят и говорят Да вот
International Community  It’s like the
Международное сообщество Это как Вот
state police yes they say so
полиция государственна да говорит так
please alcoholic Free this
пожалуйста алкоголик Освободите эту
illegally
незаконно
this apartment and he says Let’s go
эту квартиру а он говорят Пошли
everyone yes they said they said now he was
всех да говорили говорили теперь он
drunk and grabbed a squirrel Yes and began to run
пьяный схватил белку Да и начал бегать
around the floors occupying other people’s apartments
ещё по этажам занимать чужие квартиры
now the world community yes Here Uh-huh has
сейчас мировое сообщество да Вот Угу
begun the process of neutralizing
приступила к процессу нейтрализации
this  drunk, that is, the whole if the whole world
этого алкаша то есть весь если весь мир
don’t interrupt the whole world the whole world is against
не перебивай весь мир весь мир против
Russia now Yes, he’s going to smoke him out of
России сейчас Да идёт выкуривает его из
this apartment That’s
этой квартиры Вот и
all, if you take away the alcohol from a drunk, he
всё если у алкаша отобрать алкоголь он
still Well, you haven’t neutralized him, he
всё равно Ну вы его не обезвредили он
still remains a drunk right
всё равно остаётся алкашом правильно
right So the question is what  and the fact
правильно Поэтому вот вопрос что и то
that McDonald’s Coca-Cola and other things were taken from Russia,
что у России забрали кока-колу McDonald
look,
и прочую смотри
Russia as a result of this
Россия в результате в результате этой
war will cease to exist, it
войны прекратит своё существование она
will disintegrate into like the Soviet Union, like the
распадётся на как Советский Союз как
Russian Empire, which is not a
Российская империя которая не выде
special war, it will disintegrate. Why is a
онные войны да распадётся На что
drug addict one of the
наркоманов один из
signs of Zelensky, by the way?  Oh, Russia
признаков Зеленский кстати оче Россия
will fall apart Well, he’s a drug addict, everyone
распадётся Ну так он же наркоман это все
knows that, an adequate person, an adequate person
знают адекватный чело адекватный человек
would have run away from the Russian troops in the very first days,
бы ужа в первые же дни убежал бы от
only Suma could
российских войск только Сума мог так вот
stand and believe in the Victory of Ukraine, we
это стоять и верить в Победу Украины мы
all know why this doesn’t mean that he’s strong
все почему это не значит что он сильный
like a man  no matter what, he’s
типа как мужчина не ну гла он
crazy, you know. The thing is,
безбашенный понимаешь Дело в том что
look, you don’t have a chance, if he were
смотри у вас нету шансов если бы он был
normal, you could still intimidate him.
нормальным вы бы ещё могли его запугать
And so he’s all without brakes, he’ll be in
А так всё он без тормозов он будет
short until the last Russian to fight.
короче до последнего русского воевать
So we, too, have no brakes, we’re
Так у нас тоже без тормозов тип у нас
completely screwed  Nay, it’s not like that, yours will die
вообще отшиб най же не так ваш сдохнет
soon like that. I mean, how long has he not
скоро так В смысле так с сколько он не
how long has he been dying and he’s still going to
сколько он сколько он не умирает и до
die soon, well you see the
сих пор вот скоро умрёт уже ж видишь
watch is coming right Well, I wo
часики подходят правда
n’t say I won’t say that I’ll be
Ну я не скажу не скажу что прям буду
super glad, but it
супер рад но
’s time, I understand  that you all
пора буду я понимаю что вы все там его
hate him soooo super, but I really
ненавидите су супер но мне очень он
liked him until the
нравился до
year when Putin, in short, and Russian
года когда Путин короче да и российские
troops will withdraw from Crimea Donetsk Lugansk,
войска выведут из Крыма Донецка Луганска
you will go to a rally like don’t give
ты выйдешь На митинг типа не отдавать
Crimea to Ukraine, don’t give it up no, let them give it back if
Крым не отдавать нет Пускай отдают если
that’s the case Well, if they deprive us of it
это Ну если с нас при этом снимут
Absolutely all the sanctions Then let them give
совершенно все санкции Тогда пускай дают
me a [ __ ] about this Crimea And if the sanctions are not lifted
мне похуй на этот Крым А если не снимут
If these reparations are even shorter, you
санкции Если ещё будут короче эти
will come to the reparations rally,
репарации выйдешь На митинг репарации
we are just paying, like yes you will
это мы просто выплачиваем типа да будете
pay for another 14 years and 88 months Well,
выплачивать ещё 14 лет и 88 месяцев Ну
look, if the sanctions are lifted from us and we
смотри если с нас снимут санкции и мы
will  pay reparations, we
будем выплачивать репарации то мы их
won’t even feel them, it’s a big [ __ ] country. There are
даже не почувствуем большая страна [__]
so many resources here, so reparations
Тут столько ресурсов так вот репарация -
are a resource. That is, you will, for example, as
это ресурс То есть вы будете например в
part of the restoration of Ukraine for 20 years.
рамках восстановления Украины 20 лет
For example, supply oil and gas for free in Ukraine,
Например поставлять бесплатно в Украине
there are other resources there and
нефть газ там ещё другие ресурсы и
pay Oil and Gas in money, they are now
выплачивать Нефтегаз они сейчас Украину
carrying out Ukraine  Oil and gas, that is, in short, you
проводят Нефтегаз то есть короче ты
have non-gas, in general, you don’t mind
негаз есть общем ты не против получается
if your state says that we are
если государство ваше скажет что всё мы
giving them all the regions back and paying for the
отдаём им назад области и выплачиваем
operations, you won’t care, you won’t go to a rally
операции тебе будет пофиг ты На митинг
against the state, but you should
не выйдешь против государства а надо
if my state won’t
если мо государство при этом будет не
steal from me.  the same
будет воровать у меня будет такая же
territory, only Crimea will be taken away from me,
территория только у меня отнимут Крым
which I don’t need, and this is
который мне не нужен и вот это
Zaporozhye, Donetsk, Lugansk, you don’t
Запорожская Донецкая Луганска ты не
understand, you understand, you won’t have the
понял понял понял у вас не будет такая
same, not the same, territory, I mean,
же не не такая же территория я в том что
the moment when you could still have
тот момент когда у вас могла остаться
your territory has long been lost  It
ваша территория уже давно упущен надо
was necessary in the twenty-second year
было вот в двадцать втором году
they suggested to you that you simply withdraw and the
предлагали вам что вы просто выводите да
troops now everyone understands that Russia in the
войска теперь все понимают что Россия в
format as it exists, sooner
таком формате как она существует рано
or later will continue to attack its
или поздно будет дальше нападать на
neighbors, so there is already a plan to
соседей поэтому идёт уже план
dismember Russia into independent
расчленения России на независимые
national states Republics of
государства национальные Республики
Tatarstan Bashkartastan peoples of the
Татарстан башкартастан народы
Caucasus yes  yes And so on and so on
Кавказа да да И так дальше и
regional Far Eastern Republic
региональные Дальневосточная республика
Siberian Republic And so
Сибирская республика И так
on how they are going to dismember
дальше как они собираются расчленить
Russia I don’t understand how the Caucasus can be
Россию не я понимаю как Кавказ Можно
dismembered just like the Soviet Union And
расчленить так же как и Советский Союз А
how the Soviet Union collapsed in one day they
как Советский Союз распался в один день
took a piss on many different nations there were
взяли пописали много разных народов было
just 15 republics in Russia  there are more
просто 15 республик в России больше
peoples than in those republics that
народов чем в тех республиках которые
separated, I don’t think that Russia is really
отделились я не думаю что Россия прям
very lazy, why Well, the Caucasus will move away from
сильно ленится почему Ну ну отойдёт от
us and we need to get something there
нас Кавказ и Нам нужен что там
as soon as something starts to
добывать как только начнёт что-то
go away all at once, now everything
отходить всё сразу посы сейчас всё
just rests on the
держится просто на
FSB, no, that’s the FSB system  because
фсбшник нет вот э ФСБ система потому что
she is dying in Ukraine, look at
она умирает в Украине всё смотри в уже
how many problems there are already in Russia with sin Yes, why are the
сколько в России проблем с сином Да что
Zaki Islamists rebelling yes And this
там Заки исламисты восстают да И это
will only increase in your cities
будет только увеличиваться у вас города
and your cities are no longer
да у вас города уже не
Russian Why Because they are already Russian You
русские Почему Потому что уже русских Вы
almost don’t
почти не
see the amount of non-Russian element
видите количество нерусского элемента
has increased multiple times in the Soviet Union
возросло кратно в Советском Союзе
Look now
Посмотри сейчас
it is dying out and it is passive amorphous
она вымирает и она пассивная аморфна
tomorrow Akhmat will say some kind of b wait
завтра скажет Ахмат какой-то б подожди
stop stop What is the Russian nation That’s
стоп стоп Что такое русская нация Вот
exactly what the Russian nation is, this is such a
именно что такое русская нация это такой
compote
компот
of Finnish-Fino-Ugric Turkic and
из фински фино угорских тюркских и
some other types of peoples of which
каких-то ещё других типа народов которых
They called them Russians, that’s
назвали русскими вот и
all. For example, including the Ukrainians of
всё Вот например том числе и украинцы
Chechnya. Yes, including the Ukrainians.
чеченска Да в том числе и украинцы Да
But many Ukrainians were simply registered as
вот многих украинцев просто записывали в
Russians, but those who went, like, to the
русские вот тех которые выехали типа в
Soviet Union in the Russian Empire, they were
Советский Союз в Российской империи их
recorded by the Russians. They are not Russians, so they
записали русские Они не русские вот всех
registered everyone as Russians. Where  this is a Russian
записали в русские А где это русская
republic, look, there is a Republic of
республика смотри есть Республика
Tatarstan
Татарстан
Damn it
Завис
freezes hangs on the most
блин зависает на самых
interesting Russia will fall apart and we will
интересных Россия распадется и мы будем
dance on her grave subscribe to th
танцювати на ей могили подпишись на й
Telegram directly at once VN axis and popk
Telegram прям зараз ось ВН а попк
tse even more and more politely YouTube engaging us
це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня нас
through skarg or in your ban and even richer
через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже багато
video  I don’t show people right now I don’t show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams. To that end, for this purpose,
информация про стрими Тому для того щоб
we need to write an operational link
ми Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
right away and while there in the telegra okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
video
видео
tezh va and korisna information and pon va tma yy
теж ва и корисна информация и пон ва тма
operational link
йй оперативный звязок
nezalezno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine write
YouTube Слава Украине пиши